histreetdeal.com 2015-12-11

# histreetdealPrivacy Policy | histreetdeal

**Privacy Policy**

At histreetdeal.com, we value the trust you have shown in us and we respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices.

Note:

By using, adding information, or visiting the Site, you expressly agree to be bound by these Terms. The Terms may be varied at any time by the proprietors of the Site and such modified terms will be effective upon posting on the Site. .  
By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use.

1\. **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information and other Information**  
We may collect information that can identify you (“personal information”), such as name and address, personal preferences, phone numbers, email ids, when you provide it to us while using our website or in some other manner.

We may collect “Non-Personal Information” – information that cannot be used to identify you – via Cookies, even if you have not registered with or provided any Personal Information to histreetdeal.com  
We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit our website:

  * We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience.
  * We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements on our websites. While we do not provide any personal information to these companies, these companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect information about computers used to view or interact with their advertisements, some of which could be a part of the main result.
  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users’ movements around our site and understand trends.

**2\. Use of Demographic / Profile Data / Your Information**

The information collected may be use to:

  * Fulfill your requests for products and services;
  * Offer products and services that may be of interest to you;
  * Facilitate use of our website;
  * Manage your account and your preferences;
  * Analyze use of and improve our website, products and services;
  * Third parties may use Non-Personal Information in order to display advertising that reflects the interests and preferences of our user community.
  * Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our website;
  * Enforce our Terms of Use.

If you post information about yourself or others, or communicate with others using our website, please note that we cannot control who reads your postings or what they do with the information you provide. We encourage you to use caution in posting personal information

3\. **Links to Other Sites**

Our Website links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. histreetdeal.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites

4\. **Sharing of personal information**

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf; we may share aggregated, non-personal information mainly relating to aggregated statistics with advertisers and others.

5\. **Choice/Opt-Out**

Most browser software can be set to reject Cookies, and you can opt out of Cookies for several Ad Servers by visiting the ‘Network Advertising Initiative’ gateway opt-out site.

6\. **Security**

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

7\. **Terms of Use**

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

In case of any change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

8\. **Modifications**

We may modify or enhance these Terms at any time at our discretion. If we make any changes to these Terms, we will notify you by placing an appropriate message on the Site. If you have any objections to such modifications, you may notify us by writing to us at legal@histreetdeal.com. You must also immediately cease usage of the Site till such time we take up and address your concerns.
